// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is to be manipulated to achieve genetic engineering?",
    answer: "D. all the above",
    options: [
      "A. DNA",
      "B. Genes",
      "C. RNA",
      "D. All the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What do you call the circular piece containing the genetic material?",
    answer: "D. Plasmid",
    options: [
      "A. DNA",
      "B. Genes",
      "C. Microbes",
      "D. Plasmid",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following involves the transfer of DNA’s part from one organism to another?",
    answer: "D. All the above",
    options: [
      "A. Cloning",
      "B. Genetic engineering",
      "C. Genetically modified organism",
      "D. All the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the second technique in any genetic processes?",
    answer: "B. Identification of organism with desirable gene",
    options: [
      "A. New gene insertion to an existing organism’s DNA",
      "B. Identification of organism with desirable gene",
      "C. Entire DNA extraction from the organism",
      "D. Gene removal from the rest of the DNA",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following Genetic Engineering processes occurs when DNA strands are cut into fragments?",
    answer: "D. Restriction DNA",
    options: [
      "A. DNA sequencing",
      "B. Recombinant DNA technology",
      "C. Recombinant DNA",
      "D. Restriction DNA",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What happens to the genetically modified organism?",
    answer: "D. All the above",
    options: [
      "A. Enhancement of the desired physiological traits",
      "B. Genomes has been genetically engineered",
      "C. Desired biological products reproduced",
      "D. All the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the molecular basis of heredity?",
    answer: "A. DNA",
    options: [
      "A. DNA",
      "B. Genes",
      "C. RNA",
      "D. Genomes",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which is the most frequently cited examples of GMOs?",
    answer: "D. All the above",
    options: [
      "A. Agricultural plants",
      "B. Farm animals",
      "C. Medicine",
      "D. All the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What are the benefits of genetic engineering?",
    answer: "A. Reduced costs for drug and food production",
    options: [
      "A. Reduced costs for drug and food production",
      "B. Increased need for pesticides",
      "C. Decreased crop yields",
      "D. All the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What are the other examples of GMOs used in medicine?",
    answer: "C. Pharmaceutical agents",
    options: [
      "A. Milk for animals",
      "B. Paramedicines",
      "C. Pharmaceutical agents",
      "D. Vaccines",
    ],
  },
];
